Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Kimpton Administration Records 1892-1960
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - Maroon, 1951-1960 (Box 166, Folder 11-12)
  - Marquette University, 1958-1960 (Box 166, Folder 13)
  - Marshall, Thomas, Jr., 1955-1960 (Box 166, Folder 14)
  - Marshalls and aides, 1956-1960 (Box 166, Folder 15-16)
  - Marshalls and aides, student aides, 1958 (Box 166, Folder 17)
  - Masaryk, Thomas and Jan, 1934-1960 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1951-1960 (Box 167, Folder 2-5)
  - Mathematical Biology, Department of, 1951-1956 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Mathematical Sciences, Conference Board of the, 1960 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 167, Folder 8-11)
  - Mathematics, department of, report of committee on the survey of research potential and training in mathematical sciences, 1957 (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - May, Ben, Laboratory, 1954-1960 (Box 168, Folder 1-2)
  - McCarran Act, Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950, 1951-1955 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - McDowell, Mary, Settlement, audit reports, 1949-1956 (Box 168, Folder 4-5)
  - McDowell, Mary, Settlement Home, 1954-1959 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - McDowell, Mary, Settlement, minutes, budgets and reports, 1951-1960 (Box 168, Folder 7-8)
  - McMaster University, 1959 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Meadville Theological School, 1946-1960 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Meadville Theological Seminary, affiliation agreements, 1957-1960 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Medical and Biological Research, 1957-1960 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Medical and Biological Research Council, 1948-1960 (Box 169, Folder 5-7)
  - Medical and Biological Research Council, membership, 1951-1960 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Medical center, hospitals and clinics, 1959 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Medical center, hospitals and clinics, comments on service, 1956-1960 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Medical center, hospitals and clinics, executive health programs, 1954-1955 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Medical center, hospitals and clinics, laundry facilities and services, 1959 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Medical center, hospitals and clinics, religion and health, office of, 1956-1960 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Medical Schools and Clinics, 1950-1954 (Box 169, Folder 14-15)
  - Medical School and Clinics, 1955-1960 (Box 170, Folder 1-4)
  - Medical School and Clinics, Auxiliary Committee of, 1940-1959 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Medical School and Clinics, Cosmotron Project, 1953-1955 (Box 170, Folder 6-8)
  - Medical School and Clinics, Cosmotron Project, 1956-1957 (Box 171, Folder 1-5)
  - Medical School and Clinics, Dietary Study, A.T. Kearny & Co., 1960 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Medical School and Clinics, survey report, March 1958 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Medical School and Clinics, Twenty-fifth Anniversary, October 3-4, 1952 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Medical School and Clinics, Zoller Memorial Dental Clinic, 1942-1960 (Box 172, Folder 2-4)
  - Medical School and Clinics, Zoller Memorial Dental Clinic, annual report, 1954 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Medicine, Department of, 1952-1960 (Box 172, Folder 6-9)
  - Memorial services, annual university memorial service, 1958 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Memorials and Portraits, Committee on, 1956-1960 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Menn Foundation Prizes, Committee on, 1949-1954 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - Meteorology, Department of, 1950-1960 (Box 172, Folder 13-14)
  - Meteorology, Department of, space, 1952-1960 (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - Methodist Church, 1953-1960 (Box 172, Folder 16-17)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning, Council of Chicago, 1948- 1958 (Box 172, Folder 18-19)
  - M, general, 1950-1955 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1960 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Michael Reese Hospital, 1955-1960 (Box 173, Folder 3-4)
  - Michigan, University of, 1955-1960 (Box 173, Folder 5-6)
  - Michigan State University, 1956-1959 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Microbiology, Department of, 1954-1960 (Box 173, Folder 8-11)
  - Microbiology, Department of, chairmanship, 1954-1960 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, 1954-1960 (Box 173, Folder 13-14)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, 1954-1960 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, agency agreements, audits, and certificates, 1954-1960 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, one, two, and three, creation and financing of, 1954-1960 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, prior years operations, 1958-1960 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Midway Properties Trusts, trustee meetings, 1960 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Midwest Administration Center, 1953-1959 (Box 174, Folder 6-7)
  - Midwest Conference on Graduate Study and Research, 1948-1959 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Midwest Conference on Industrial Relations, 1940-1958 (Box 174, Folder 9-10)
  - Midwest Interlibrary Center, 1952 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Midwest Program on Airborne Television Instruction, 1959-1960 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - Midwest Research Institute, 1955-1957 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Mid-year class, abolition of, 1960 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1956-1960 (Box 175, Folder 2-4)
  - Misrepresentations, American Institute of Financial Brokers, 1959-1960 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Misrepresentations, Crown Publishers, The Wayward Ones, 1952-1953 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Misrepresentations, Foundation for Better Reading, 1950-1951 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Missouri, University of, 1959-1960 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Molitor, Andre, 1959-1960 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Mont Pelerin Society, 1957-1960 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Moral Re-Armament, 1951 (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - Moreell, Admiral Ben, background, 1954-1956 (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - Moreell, Admiral Ben, correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 175, Folder 13)
  - Moreell, Admiral Ben, Hoover Commission Task Force, lectures on water resources, 1956 (Box 175, Folder 14)
  - Moreell, Ben, "Our Nation’s Water Resources," 1956-1960 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Moreell, Ben, pamphlets, books and lectures on water resources, 1956-1958 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Moreell, Admiral Ben, publication of lecture "Our Nation's Water Resources," advertising and sales stimulation, 1956-1957 (Box 176, Folder 3-4)
  - Morgan Park Academy, 1951-1960 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Morningside Heights, 1951-1958 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Motion pictures filmed at the University, University Film Service, 1954-1955 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Mount Carmel High School, 1958-1959 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Mount Sinai Hospital, 1951 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Movies, 1960 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Mundelein College, 1957-1959 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, 1956-1960 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, Board of Trustees, 1951-1960 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, Board of Trustees, minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 177, Folder 9-11)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, use of museum space by U of C, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Music, Department of, 1955-1960 (Box 177, Folder 13-14)
  - Music, Department of, establishment, 1951 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Musical organizations, University Symphony Orchestra and Chorus, 1954-1960 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1951-1960 (Box 178, Folder 3-5)
  - National Academy of Sciences, membership, 1944-1960 (Box 178, Folder 6-8)
  - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 1953-1958 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1958-1960 (Box 178, Folder 10-11)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1957-1958 (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs, 1951-1960 (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - National Association of Life Underwriters, 1953-1954 (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1956-1960 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators, 1955-1960 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Women Deans and Counselors, 1955-1958 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - National Broadcasting Company, 1955-1959 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - National Citizens Council for Better Schools, 1949-1959 (Box 179, Folder 5-6)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1951-1960 (Box 179, Folder 7-9)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1950-1960 (Box 179, Folder 10-12)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1953-1960 (Box 180, Folder 1-4)
  - National Commission on Teacher Education and Professional Standards, 1954-1960 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - National Conference on the Administration of Research, 1955-1959 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1952-1960 (Box 180, Folder 7-8)
  - National Conference on Citizenship, 1953-1960 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - National Conference on Higher Education, 1955-1960 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1956-1960 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ, 1954-1958 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ, negotiations on site for headquarters, 1953-1960 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - National Council for Community Improvement, 1955-1956 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - National Council of State Garden Clubs, 1954 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - National Council of Teachers of English, 1956-1958 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - National Defense, Committee on, 1950-1952 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, 1958-1960 (Box 181, Folder 8-10)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, disclaimer affidavit and loyalty oath, 1958-1960 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, disclaimer affidavit and loyalty oath, 1958-1960 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, Language and Area Centers Program, 1960 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, Language and Area Centers Program, Title IV, 1958-1959 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, National Defense Graduate Fellowship Program, Title IV, 1958-1959 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, regional meeting, Mandel Hall, 1958 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1958, Strengthening Instruction in Science, Math, and Modern Foreign Languages, Title III, 1958-1960 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - National Defense Education Act of 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - National Defense Graduate Fellowship Program, 1960 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - National Defense Student Loan Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - National Education Association, 1951-1960 (Box 183, Folder 2-6)
  - National Education Association, salary studies, 1957-1959 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - National Educational Television and Radio Center, 1960 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - National Engineering Societies, 1953-1956 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - National Federation of College and University Business Officers, 1959-1960 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - National Federation of College and University Business Officers Associations, 1955-1958 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1950-1959 (Box 184, Folder 3-4)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, Advisory Committee on Basic Medical Research Program, 1958-1960 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, Conference on "Tomorrow's Challenges to the Medical Sciences," Chicago, March 5, 1957 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - National Industrial Conference, 1952-1960 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - National League for Nursing, 1952-1960 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - National Library of Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - National Meteorological Center, 1952 (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - National Military-Industrial Conference, 1955-1960 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - National Opinion Research Center, 1954-1960 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - National Opinion Research Center, financing and space, 1951-1960 (Box 184, Folder 13)
  - National Opinion Research Center, general, 1947-1954 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - National Opinion Research Center, surveys, 1948-1959 (Box 185, Folder 2-5)
  - National Opinion Research Center, surveys, Hyde Park-Kenwood area survey, 1955 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - National Planning Association, 1952-1960 (Box 185, Folder 7-9)
  - National Research Council, 1923-1959 (Box 185, Folder 10-11)
  - National Research Council, Division of Mathematics, 1951-1958 (Box 185, Folder 12)
  - National Research Council, Division of Mathematics, annual reports, 1954-1958 (Box 186, Folder 1-2)
  - National Research Council, Mathematics Survey, 1955-1956 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - National Retail Dry Goods Association, 1956-1957 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students, 1951-1960 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - National Science Fair, 1955 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation, 1950-1960 (Box 186, Folder 7-12)
  - National Science Foundation, Academic Year Institute for High School Teachers, 1956-1959 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, fellowships, 1951-1960 (Box 187, Folder 2-3)
  - National Science Foundation, legislative and background material, 1946-1959 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation, scientific research activities at colleges and universities, meeting, questionnaires, etc., 1954-1958 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation, Special Commission for Rubber Research, 1954-1956 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation, Special Commission for Rubber Research, 1954-1956 (Box 188, Folder 1-3)
  - National Scientific Reserve Fund, proposal to establish, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - National Student Association, 1954-1960 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - National University Extension Association, 1959-1960 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Civilizations, Department of, 1955-1960 (Box 188, Folder 7-8)
  - Needs, 1948-1960 (Box 188, Folder 9-10)
  - Neighborhood Campaign, Committee to Direct, 1960 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Neighborhood Committee, 1960 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Neighborhood Committee, minutes, 1956-1960 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood, Committee on Planning, 1951-1955 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood document, 1959-1960 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood funds, program of financing, 1956-1960 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Program, 1959-1960 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhood Program, Urban Renewal Project, "University City," 1956-1957 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Neighborhood, re-use sites, 1960 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - New College Plan, a Proposal for a Major Departure in Higher Education, 1958-1959 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - New Testament, Department of, 1953-1960 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - New Testament Project, 1954-1955 (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
  - New Trier High School, 1957-1958 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1953 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - New York Central System, 1948-1953 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - New York, State University of, 1955-1960 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - New York University, 1954-1960 (Box 190, Folder 7-8)
  - Newberry Library, proposed association between the University of Chicago and Newberry, 1959-1960 (Box 190, Folder 9-10)
  - Newberry, Crerar and the University of Chicago Libraries, discussions on possible consolidation, 1946-1958 (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - Newcomen Society, 1959 (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - News from the University of Chicago, published by Office of the Dean of Students, 1957-1959 (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - N, general, 1950-1955 (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - Nominations, Committee on, meetings, candidates, and nominations, 1951-1960 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - North American Conference on the Social Implications of Industrialization and Technological Change, September 1960 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina, University of, 1956-1958 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - North Central Association of Academic Deans, 1956 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1951-1959 (Box 191, Folder 5-9)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, accreditation visits, 1955-1958 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - North central association of colleges and schools, institutional annual report, 1956-1959 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Northwestern University, 1951-1958 (Box 191, Folder 12-13)
  - Northwestern University, 1955-1960 (Box 192, Folder 1-2)
  - Northwestern University Associates, 1955-1960 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1951-1960 (Box 192, Folder 4-6)
  - Nuclear medicine, section on, 1959-1960 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Nyasaland, 1959-1960 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1956-1960 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, Department of, 1951-1959 (Box 192, Folder 10-11)
  - O, general, 1950-1955 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Ohio State University, 1951-1960 (Box 192, Folder 13-14)
  - Old People's Home, 1957-1959 (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, computer, UNIVAC I system, dedication, 1958 (Box 192, Folder 16)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, UNIVAC, 1956-1960 (Box 192, Folder 17)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, UNIVAC, installation, 1956-1959 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Operations Research Society of America, 1952-1956 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1950-1954 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Oregon State College, 1958-1960 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Organic Chemistry, Institute of, 1956-1958 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Organization of Universities, general, 1943-1959 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Oriental Institute, 1951-1960 (Box 193, Folder 7-12)
  - Oriental Institute, Assuan High Dam program, 1960 (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Oriental Institute, development office, 1954 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Oriental Institute, directorship, 1952-1960 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Oriental Institute, items pulled for John T. Wilson, 1931-1951 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Oriental Institute, proposed Archeology House, 1956 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Oriental Institute, symposium, "The Expansion of Society in the Ancient East and its Cultural Implications," 1957-1958 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Oriental Institute, visiting committee, 1951-1960 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Oriental Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1940-1954 (Box 194, Folder 7-8)
  - Orientation program, 1951-1960 (Box 194, Folder 9-12)
  - Orthogenic School, 1951-1960 (Box 195, Folder 1-4)
  - Overhead expenses, 1956-1959 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Overhead expenses, principles for determining, committee for ACE, AAU and NFCUBO, 1958-1959 (Box 195, Folder 6-7)
  - Overhead expenses, principles for determining, government contracts, 1955-1958 (Box 195, Folder 8-9)
  - Owl and Serpent, 1952-1960 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Paleozoology, Committee on, 1958 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Pan American Games, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Pan-American Institute of Geography and History, 1949-1958 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Parent-Teacher Association, 1948-1960 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Parking, 1951-1960 (Box 196, Folder 5-9)
  - Passavant Memorial Hospital, 1951-1953 (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - Patent and copyright policy, advertising and endorsements, 1951-1954 (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - Patent policy, 1954-1960 (Box 196, Folder 12)
  - Patents, 1950-1960 (Box 196, Folder 13-15)
  - Patents, Committee on, 1940-1960 (Box 197, Folder 1-2)
  - Patents, National Research Council, patent policies, practices, and procedures, 1952-1955 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Patents, Policy, Four E Contracts, 1947-1952 (Box 197, Folder 4-5)
  - Patents of the University of Chicago, research corporation patent development agreement, 1955-1960 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Patents of the University of Chicago, Talalay, 1952-1954 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Pathology, Department of, 1957-1960 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Pediatrics, department of, 1959-1960 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1956-1960 (Box 197, Folder 10-12)
  - Personnel, 1950-1960 (Box 197, Folder 13)
  - Personnel, 1951-1960 (Box 198, Folder 1-4)
  - Personnel, classification of, 1954-1957 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Personnel, employment of more than one member of a family, 1955-1959 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Personnel, notices, 1951-1960 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Personnel, nurses, 1952-1960 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Personnel, overtime, 1944-1955 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Personnel, professional staff, 1951-1956 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Personnel, wage rates, 1956-1960 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - P, general, 1950-1955 (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - Pharmacology, Department of, 1955-1960 (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1951-1960 (Box 198, Folder 14)
  - Philosophy, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 198, Folder 15-17)
  - Philosophy, Department of, space, 1957-1960 (Box 198, Folder 18)
  - Phoenix, a U of C publication, 1959 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Physical Education, Department of, 1925-1960 (Box 199, Folder 2-5)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Department of, facilities committee, 1957-1960 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education, Department of, racquet courts, 1952-1960 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Physical Education, Department of, space and facilities, 1951-1960 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, 1951-1954 (Box 199, Folder 9-14)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, Advisory Committee minutes, 1954 (Box 199, Folder 15)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, Central Shop, 1947-1960 (Box 199, Folder 16-17)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, Deanship, 1951-1955 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, faculty board, 1952-1960 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, science open house, 1958-1960 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, space and renovation, 1953 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, visiting committee, 1958-1960 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Physics, Department of, 1939-1960 (Box 200, Folder 6-9)
  - Physics, Department of, chairmanship, 1955-1959 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Physiology, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 200, Folder 11-13)
  - Physiology, Department of, Carlson, Anton Julius, 1952-1956 (Box 200, Folder 14)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, 1949-1960 (Box 200, Folder 15-16)
  - Poetry magazine, 1952 (Box 200, Folder 17)
  - Police Academy, proposed, 1952-1960 (Box 200, Folder 18)
  - Police, campus security, 1952-1960 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Police, campus security, canine patrol, 1959-1960 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Police, campus security, Public Safety Director, proposed, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Police campus security, Stauffer, Farrant, Larsen, 1959 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Police-campus society, 1952-1960 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Police Department, Chicago, 1949-1954 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Police dogs, 1959-1960 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Political campaigns and elections, alumni letter re: Gutnecht, 1956-1957 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Political campaigns and elections, city, state, and national, 1955-1959 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Political campaigns and elections, city, state, and national, 1958-1960 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Political Science, Department of, 1949-1960 (Box 201, Folder 11-15)
  - Political Science, Department of, chairmanship, 1958 (Box 201, Folder 16)
  - Pollution, cleaner air committee of Hyde Park-Kenwood, 1959-1960 (Box 201, Folder 17)
  - Pomona College, 1953-1964 (Box 201, Folder 18)
  - Population research and training center, 1955-1960 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Porter Foundation, 1953-1959 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Post-doctorals, 1952-1960 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Potential personnel, 1951 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Precollegiate Education, Board of, 1953-1960 (Box 202, Folder 5-7)
  - Precollegiate Education, Board of, agenda, 1955-1959 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Precollegiate Education, Board of, agenda and minutes, 1954-1960 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Precollegiate Education, Board of, membership, 1951-1955 (Box 202, Folder 10-11)
  - Precollegiate Education, Board of, minutes, 1954 (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Preparation of Teachers, Committee on, general, 1951-1954 (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - Preparation of Teachers, Committee on, membership, 1951-1954 (Box 202, Folder 14)